[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Only one actor was ranked in the 20 Top Cops for two different roles.  What actor played Lt. Vincent Hanna opposite Robert De Niros Neil McCauley and NYPD Officer Frank Serpico?", "correct_answer": "Al Pacino", "incorrect_answers": ["Harrison Ford", "Sean Connery", "Robert Duval"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who sang the theme song to St. Elmos Fire, subtitled Man in Motion?", "correct_answer": "John Parr", "incorrect_answers": ["Huey Lewis", "Daryl Hall", "Steve Perry"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what type of outfit was Resurrection Mary buried according to the popular urban legend from the region of Chicago, Illinois?", "correct_answer": "White dancing dress", "incorrect_answers": ["Blood-red satin dress", "Black lace gown", "Bridal gown"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the Greek word Phascolarctos, denoting the genus to which koalas belong, mean?", "correct_answer": "Pouch bear", "incorrect_answers": ["Ash-colored", "Doesnt drink", "Monkey bear"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the dog, that became the first earthling to enter orbit?", "correct_answer": "Laika", "incorrect_answers": ["Lisichka", "Rover", "Belka"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The birthstone of this month is the yellow topaz, and its birth flower is the chrysanthemum.", "correct_answer": "November", "incorrect_answers": ["December", "January", "March"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Faye Dunaway co-starred in 3 of the Top 100 AFI movies.. But she  was also  responsible for some hysterical overacting in one of  the most embarrassing failures in modern American cinema.", "correct_answer": "Mommy Dearest", "incorrect_answers": ["Network", "Chinatown", "Bonnie and Cyde"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Two earthquakes with epicenter in northeast Arkansas, caused landslides and geological changes along the Mississippi River. On what date did these two earthquakes take place?", "correct_answer": "December 16, 1811", "incorrect_answers": ["April 27, 1815", "July 23, 1809", "August 12, 1823"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The horror movie Killer Klowns from Outer Space came out in 1984.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What part of their body do the insects from order Archaeognatha use to spring up into the air?", "correct_answer": "Tail", "incorrect_answers": ["Antennae", "Front legs", "Hind legs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Every year in Yatesville, Georgia there is a celebration of chitlins, called the Chitlin Hoedown.  What exactly are chitlins?", "correct_answer": "Pigs intestines", "incorrect_answers": ["Bull testicles", "Sheep eyes", "Cow brains"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Guess the missing number in the following sequence: 3, 6, 18, 36, ___, 216, 234, 468, 1404.", "correct_answer": "72", "incorrect_answers": ["108", "54", "39"]}]